<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<homepage>
  <navbar>
    <logo>./img/fhlc-logo.png</logo>
    <brand>Full House Learning Center</brand>
    <menu>
      <item>
        <text>Home</text>
        <link>index.xhtml</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <text>About FHLC</text>
        <link>about.xhtml</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <text>Services</text>
        <link>services.xhtml</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <text>Contact</text>
        <link>contact.xhtml</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <text>Login</text>
        <link>login.xhtml</link>
      </item>
    </menu>
  </navbar>
  <content>
    <about-us>
      <header>About Us</header>
      <description>
        <p>
          Welcome to Full House Learning Center, where every child's potential is nurtured, and
          their
          journey of learning is filled with love growth and purpose. Established in 2001 under the
          name Complete in Christ Kiddie Center, our school began by catering to young children ages
          3-5. Since 2016, we have evolved into a formal educational institution offering both
          preschool and elementary programs, committed to developing well-rounded and capable
          learners.
        </p>

        <p>
          Our school's achievements are a testament to our dedication to excellence. Many of our
          students have successfully passed entrance exams to Pasig City Science High School, while
          others studying abroad meet and exceed international standards, ensuring smooth
          transitions
          to their new schools. Our alumni who have transferred to prestigious institutions like
          Ateneo de Manila University and the University of the Philippines Integrated School are
          often commended for their proficiency in reading, reflecting the strong academic
          foundation
          they built with us.
        </p>

        <p>
          At Full House Learning Center, we create an atmosphere where students feel a strong sense
          of
          belonging, every child has the opportunity to showcase their talents and skills through
          various school programs. Our curriculum continues to grow to meet the demands of the 21st
          century, with programs in reading and literacy, coding and robotics, Singapore Math, and
          scouting activities, all aimed at equipping students with essential skills for the future.
          Looking ahead, we remain committed to enhancing each student's holistic development,
          continuously introducing programs that will prepare them to be responsible, God-fearing
          citizens. Our vision is clear, we focus on the unique gifts and capabilities of every
          child,
          allowing them to engage in experiential activities that develop them fully as they grow
          into
          compassionate and capable individuals.
        </p>
      </description>
      <mission>
        <intro>FHLC believes in every child's right to quality education and holistic growth. Our
          mission is:</intro>
        <goals>
          <li>To provide children with joyful and meaningful learning experiences.</li>
          <li>To instill in them key growth areas: spiritual (knowing Jesus), moral (living a good
            life), and successful living.</li>
          <li>To support parents by offering quality education at an affordable cost.</li>
          <li>To allow God to use teachers as instruments in ministering to and training each child
            in the way they should go.</li>
        </goals>
      </mission>

      <vision>Focusing on the gifts and capabilities of a whole child as we allow them to explore
        experiential activities and develop them fully as a responsible and God-fearing citizen.</vision>
      <values>Integrity, Respect, Excellence, Collaboration</values>
    </about-us>
  </content>
</homepage>
